Watch as God uses Prophet T.B. Joshua to separate the darkness from light in the lives of these people.
The right hand of God is power.
The lighting of God is moving through Prophet T.B. Joshua
to meet the needs of people from all over the world.
As he walks among the visitors during the first service giving words of prophecy,
he swiftly moves to a certain man at the back.
Brother, don't run from me. God loves you, give me your hand.
You will come to the prayer line today.I will see you there, OK?
I will see you. I am your friend. Please don't run from me. I love you.
He says he is scared.
You are scared?
Yes.
What is disturbing him is that mine is positive, his own is negative and I want to deliver him.
That’s correct.
It's true.
Later in the second service, the same man awaits his meeting with the man of God
in the prayer line of The SCOAN.
Many others too await this encounter with the problem solver Jesus Christ.
They have come from different countries with different hopes, different expectations, but with one assurance,
Jesus is who He says He is and He can do what He says He can do.
Let us see what will happen next.
This is the promised meeting the man of God prophesied about in the first service.
Martien is now receiving prayer from the Prophet
and is undergoing deliverance from the many problems he came with.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
What is happening during the prayer goes to show that we are in a warfare.
Prophet T.B. Joshua is not fighting a natural situation.
He is not fighting against flesh and blood but against what we cannot see.
It's a spiritual battle.
Let's watch the operation of the Holy Spirit.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Look as he grabs the chair fearlessly attempts to attack the Prophet
He is being pushed by the negative spirit the man of God had spoken about earlier,
but because of the power and the anointing of God in the life of Prophet T.B Joshua,
he is unable to succeed.
There is nothing God cannot command, control and instruct,
all power in Heaven and on earth has been invested in that name Jesus Christ.
Right now you can see his muscles are extremely tense, he's gripping his chair, tensions on the rise.
It seems like he wants to attack the Prophet again.
Maybe he wants to go for round two.
The aggression in him is just too much.
Well, satan can only attempt but he cannot succeed
because greater is He who is in the Prophet than he who is in this man.
Oh look at the tattoo on his arm.
Look at the ring in his eyebrow, the expression on his face.
Hold on - the Prophet is calling him.
Could this be round two?
Well, there is only one way to find out, let's watch.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Do you think the battle is over?
Hmmm..... wow, he's smiling.
Do you want to hit me?
No, it's something inside me.
Something inside of you?
And I want to deliver you,
so remaining just two; you'll be free, OK.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Stand up; come back.
Demons are going out because they are commanded to go in the name of Jesus Christ.
This is the power of God in action.
Deliverance in the power of the Holy Spirit.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
His expression says it all. Satan is powerless in the face of God's amour and weapons.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ, be free!
Be delivered, in Jesus' name!
Amen. Thank You, Lord.
Don't ask yourself whether you are free or not. This is a testimony that you are free.
As Martien stands up, the look on his face clearly shows
that his life has been turned from one of frustration to fulfilment.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Now am delivered! Thank God. I am free.
I thank God of Prophet Joshua; T.B Joshua is a real man of God.
TESTIMONY TIME
Sir, you are welcome here to The SCOAN here in Lagos, Nigeria.
Can you please tell us your name, your age and the country you come from?
My name is Martien. I am from Holland and I am 42 years old.
What was the problem that you were having before you came to The SCOAN
and can you just tell us some of the experiences that you were having.
The reason I came to The SCOAN is that I had a very bad violent nature
and because of that I was so scared. I tried to kill myself several times.
After that I felt I had no meaning in my life, no role, no purpose.
I became very violent and it became worse and worse and worse
until I heard voices in my head that led me to do some things.
When I was walking in the street, I hit people very bad. I could knock people down.
I was in jail for it also. I almost killed people.
So you are saying that the spirit of anger was such a strong spirit
that it caused you to do things to the point that you ended up in jail?
Yes
So when you came to The SCOAN, we understand that during the service of the man of God,
Prophet T.B. Joshua, that he actually came over to you and he said something to you.
Can you just tell us, what did the Prophet say to you?
He said that I am your friend, you don't have to be scared.
Because when I came into the church, I felt a very big power of God and I tried to hide from it
because I thought God wanted to judge me or something like that.
Brother, don't run from me. God loves you. Give me your hand.
You will come to the prayer line today. I will see you there.
OK?
I will see you. I am your friend. Please don't run from me. I love you.
He says he is scared.
You are scared?
Yes.
What is disturbing him is mine is positive, his own is negative and I want to deliver him.
That’s correct.
It's true.
When your life is controlled by demons,
it is not easy to describe or explain when something takes control of you.
I was pushed to digging up graves, to dig up the coffins and open them.
It's difficult to explain because it was something inside of me that controlled my life.
So you are saying that the demons in your life controlled you to such an effect
that it would cause you to dig up graves, go to the graveyard, attack people and do all sorts of evil.
- Is that right?
- Yes, that's right.
So you came to The SCOAN - we will just bring you back to what happened during the service.
After the man of God met you and said do not be afraid,
we understand that the same day you were arranged in the prayer line.
Can you just tell us what was your experience at the prayer line.
What was actually going through your mind at the time and just tell us how you were feeling?
Well, the night before that I slept so bad because I knew something was going to happen.
Something controlled my body again and I became so angry and I wanted to attack him.
It was a miracle because I grabbed the chair and I actually wanted to hit him with it.
I also wanted to kick him but there was a power that stopped me.
When he was doing like this, a power came over me and I fell down.
Normally for me that is not normal because I am strong enough.
But then I fell down on the ground and a very big peace came over me
and something in me at that moment was coming out of me and now it's gone.
Oh hallelujah, clap for wonderful Jesus Christ.
Testimony Time
So you were wonderfully, fantastically delivered in the power of the Holy Spirit
by the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
So how do you feel now?
You said you have a wonderful peace that has come over you.
How do you feel in your mind now, in your body? How are you feeling right now?
I am feeling very very quiet. Peaceful, and not a feeling of becoming angry anymore, not at all.
And are you hearing any voices anymore to tell you to do what you used to do?
No no, not anymore, Jesus set me free.
Oh hallelujah, clap for wonderful Jesus Christ.
So Jesus Christ has completely delivered you and set you free, we thank God.
Let's clap for Jesus Christ once again for that wonderful healing, wonderful deliverance.
At last I want to say one last thing.
It is a nightmare when your whole life is controlled by violent nature.
And satan, I want to tell you now, I am free, God set me free.
Oh hallelujah!
Amen.
Testimony Time
So now that Jesus Christ has completely delivered you and set you free, you are now peaceful.
What is your promise to Him?
I want to serve God.
Amen!
Well, we pray with you that God will give you that special grace to do just that
and to go and sin no more, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Amen.
Thank you very much. Clap for wonderful Jesus Christ once again.
After testifying to the goodness of God in his life,
Martien prepares to return to Holland to live his life anew.
Just before he goes, he shares his experience one more time
I feel happy inside and since Sunday, I have become very very sensitive.
Since several times, I had to cry cry cry, it's the love of God.
I cannot explain it but I am happy.
I feel that something has come out of me; I have no feelings of anger again.
It's real; it's not fake.
When the rest of the Holy Spirit came over me, you could see I was knocked down on the ground
but with peace, peace in my heart.
It was really a touch of God on me.
Otherwise, if the prophet was not really a man of God,
I would have knocked him down; I can tell you that.
He is a man of God. I have never seen a man like him.
I have visited so many churches in Holland but I never saw power like this.
It is a very big expression.
He is really a man of God.
One thing I have learned is to look on God, no matter how great your faith is.
You have to express your faith in God in your life and then all miracles can happen in your life.
That's what I have learned here.
That’s fantastic, sir.
We pray with you that God Almighty will give you a safe journey home
and the grace to maintain all the peace and joy you have received here, in Jesus' name.
Amen!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.
RV: Mel Flowers 17/03/2019